A Guide to the Records of the Office of the President, Walter S. Newman, 1947-1962 (Bulk 1947-1961)
Special Collections and University Archives, Virginia Tech
- Series I. General Correspondence, 1947-1961
  - General Correspondence, 1949
    - Governor's Advisory Council (Box 3, Folder 33-34)
    - Governor's Advisory Council, Research Committee on Education (Box 3, Folder 35-37)
    - Hart, Harris, Director of Personnel (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Homecoming Committee (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Hutcheson, J.R., Chancellor (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Hutcheson, T.B., Dean, Agriculture (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Inauguration, Dr. W.S. Newman April 18 (Box 3, Folder 42-43)
    - Johnston, J. Ambler; Carneal and Johnston (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Knote, T.W., Head, Business Administration Department (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Legislation (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Loan Funds, Student, Proposed Plan for Administration of (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - M, miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Mc, miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Manning, H.L., Head, Industrial Engineering Department (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Medals (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Mellon Gift to Virginia Polytechnic Institute (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Miles, C.P., Dean of the College, Academic Sciences (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Mumford, T.W. (1) Commandant (Box 3, Folder 54-57)
    - Murray, W.A., Head, Electrical Engineering (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Newman, Walter S. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Norris, E.B. (Box 4, Folder 2-3)
    - Orientation (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - O'Shaughnessy, L. (Graduate Studies) (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Overholser, E.L., Head, Horticulture Department (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Pletta, D.H., Head, Applied Mechanics (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - President's Home (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Radford College, Dr. David W. Peters, President (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Registrar's Office, Miss Clarice Slusher, Registrar (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Research Foundation, Inc., Virginia Polytechnic Institute (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Robeson, F.L., Head, Physics Department (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Sanders, H.M., Head, Agriculture Department (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Scholarships, Fellowships and Loans (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Seitz, C.E., Head, Agricultural Engineering Department (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Southern Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - State Board of Education (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Statistics Department (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Student Activities Committee (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Student Life Committees (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Tate, Mrs. Mildred T. (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Treasurer of Virginia Tech (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Tuck, William W., Governor of Virginia (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - University Club (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Vandenburg, H.P.C., Institute Engineer (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Veterinary Education (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Virginia Truck Experiment Station (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - General Correspondence, 1950
    - Administrative Council (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Agricultural Engineering Department, tribute to Professor Seitz (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Agricultural:Vocational Education, Mr. W.H. Sanders, Head (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Alumni Association, General; Mr. H.B. Redd, Exec. Secretary (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Alumni Association, Word War II Memorial (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - American Association of University Professors (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Applied Mechanics Department, Mr. D.H. Pletta, Head (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Association of American Universities (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Athletic Association, Virginia Tech (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Attorney General J.L. Almond (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Bates, R.E., Director of Student Affairs (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Bradford, J.H., Director of the Budget (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Brannan Plan (U.S. agricultural policy) (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Budget Matters (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Cassell, S.K., Business Manager, regarding the naming of Thomas, Femoyer and Monteith Dormitories (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Cato, W.H., Director of Guidance and Placement (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Chemistry Department, Dr. J.W. Watson, Head (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Claytor Lake Youth Camp (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Commencement Exercises (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Community Concert Association (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Derring, P.H., YMCA (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Dietrick, L.B., Director, Extension Service (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Educational Foundation, Inc., Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Dr. J.R. Hutcheson, President (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Engineering Experiment Station (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Engineering Experiment Station, Establishment of (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Enrollment, Danville Extension (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Enrollment Statistics (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - F, miscellaneous (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Farrier, P.H., Director of Admissions (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Fishburn, J.B., Price Mountain Coal Property (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - French, C.C., Vice President (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Football, Applications for Head Coaching Job, F.O. Moseley (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Geology Department, Dr. B.N. Cooper, Head (first newsletter) (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Governor's Advisory Council, Research Committee on Education (Box 4, Folder 61-63)
    - Governor of Virginia John S. Battle (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Heth Property (Whitethorn) (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Homecoming Committee (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - Hutcheson, J.R., Chancellor (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - Hutcheson, T.B., Dean of Agriculture (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Infirmary, Annual Report; Dr. C.R. Woolwine, Physician (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - Johnston, G. Burke; Hiring, Dean of Academic Sciences and Business Administration (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Johnston, J. Ambler (Carneal & Johnston) (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Land-Grant Colleges and Universities, Association of; correspondence (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Legislation (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Miles, C.P., Dean of the College (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Military Department, Col. T.W. Mumford, Commandant (20-year comparison of grades, civilian-cadet snowball fight) (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - National Collegiate Athletic Association, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Radford College, Audits, 1949-1950 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Radford College, Dr. David W. Peters, President (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Regional Council for Education (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Research Foundation, Inc., Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Dean E.B. Norris, President (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Retirement System, Virginia Polytechnic Institute (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Southern Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Southern Regional Education Board (Box 5, Folder 14-15)
    - State Board of Agriculture (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - State Department of Education, Virginia Advisory Committee on Schools and Colleges (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - T, miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Treasurer of Virginia, Mr. Jessie W. Dillon (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Virginia Truck Experiment Station (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - General Correspondence, 1951
    - Accrediting, National Committee on; Engineers Council on Professional Development (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Advisory Council on Virginia Economy, General (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Advisory Council on Virginia Economy, Research Committee on Education (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Agricultural:Vocational Education Department, H.W. Sanders, Head (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Alumni Association, General; H.B. Redd, Secretary (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Athletic Association, Virginia Tech, Audit (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Attorney General J. Lindsay Almond (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Audits (Virginia Agricultural Extension Station; Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 1949-1951 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Bates, R.E., Director of Student Affairs (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Board of Visitors, Resolutions (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Budget Matters (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Cassell, S.K., Business Manager (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Cato, W.H., Business Manager (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Commencement Exercises (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Community Concert Association (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - E, miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Engineering Experiment Station, E.B. Norris, Director (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Enrollment Statistics (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Faculty, Administration (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Faculty, Teaching (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Farrier, P.H., Director of Admissions (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Federal Communication Commission, Television (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Fishburn, J.B. (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Football (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Fox, Walter S. (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - G, miscellaneous (organization of life-saving crew in Blacksburg) (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - General Education Board (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Geology Department, B.N. Cooper, Head (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Governor of Virginia, John S. Battle (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Graduate Committee on Education; J.Lindsey Stiles, Chairman (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - H, miscellaneous (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Hart, Harris, Director of Personnel (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Home Economics Department; Mildred T. Tate, Head (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Hutcheson, J.R., Chancellor (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Industrial Engineering Department, H.L. Manning, Head (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Infirmary, C.R. Woolwine, Physician (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Land-Grant Colleges and Universities, Association of (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Legislation on Military Matters (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Military Department, W.B. Merritt, Commandant (criticism of military system) (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - National Collegiate Athletic Association (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Naval ROTC (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - Pardue, Louis A., Vice-President (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Pasture Improvement Committee, (Governor's) W.S. Newman, Chairman; includes photograph of committee (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - Presidents Council, Proceedings March 28 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - Racial Relations (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Radford College, D.W. Peters, President, and materials regarding successor (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Radio Committee, L.B. Dietrick, Chairman (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Research Foundation, Virginia Polytechnic Institute; E.B. Norris, Director (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Scholarships, Fellowships, and Loans (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - State Department of Education (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Students, General (letters to and from) (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Advisory Legislative Council (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Agricultural Conference Board (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Truck Extension Station (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - World-News Series on Virginia Polytechnic Institute (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence, 1952
    - Advisory Council on the Virginia Economy (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Agriculture, Applications for Deanship (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Agricultural Engineering Department, S.E. Seitz, Head (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Agricultural:Vocational Education Department, H.W. Sanders, Head (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Agronomy Department, H.L. Dunton, Head (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Alumni Association, General; H.B. Redd, Secretary (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Alumni Association, World War II Memorial (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Animal Husbandry Department (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Applied Mechanics Department, D.H. Pletta, Head (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - Athletic Association, Virginia Tech (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - Attorney General J. L. Almond (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - Audits (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - Band, Virginia Polytechnic Institute (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Biology Department, I.D. Wilson, Head (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Bradford, J.H., Director of Budget (State), purchase of farm land (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Budget Matters (Box 6, Folder 27)
    - Cadet Corps Senate Minutes (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Cadet Uniform, Revision of (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Cassell, S.K., Business Manager (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Chemical Engineering Department, F.C. Vilbrandt, Head (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Civil Engineering Department, R.C. Brinker, Head (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Civilian Student Body (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Commandant, Selection of (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Commandant of Cadets, Major General John M. Devine (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Commencement Exercises (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Community Concert Association (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Cultural and Social Program Committee (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - Dairy Department, C.W. Holdaway, Head; Smithfield (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Daugherty, W.H., Director, Extension Division (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Educational Foundation, V.P.I., J.R. Hutcheson, President (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Educational Foundation, V.P.I., Scholarships (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - Engineering Experiment Station, E.B. Norris, Director (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Engineering Faculty, Committees of (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Enrollment Statistics (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Extension Division, General Correspondence (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - Faculty - Administration (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - Farrier, P.H., Director of Admissions (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - Geology Department, B.N. Cooper, Head (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - Gifts to the College, copy of L.D. Keyser Will (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Governor of Virginia, John S. Battle (Box 6, Folder 51)
    - Hart, Harris, Director of Personnel (Box 6, Folder 52)
    - Hutcheson, J.R., Chancellor (Box 6, Folder 53)
    - N, miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 54)
    - Newman, W.S., President (Box 6, Folder 55)
    - National Collegiate Athletic Association (Box 6, Folder 56)
    - Norris, E.B., Dean of Engineering (Box 6, Folder 57)
    - O, miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 58)
    - P, miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 59)
    - Pardue, L.A., Director of Graduate Study (Box 6, Folder 60)
    - Pardue, L.A., Vice President (Box 6, Folder 61)
    - Pasture Improvement Committee (Governor's), W.S. Newman, Chairman (Box 6, Folder 62)
    - Physics Department, E.L. Robeson, Head (Box 6, Folder 63)
    - Presidents' Council (of State-Supported Institutions of Higher Education) (Box 6, Folder 64)
    - Racial Relations (Box 6, Folder 65)
    - Radford College (Box 6, Folder 66)
    - Radio Committee (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - Regional Council for Higher Education (Box 6, Folder 68-69)
    - Requisitions and Orders (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - Research Foundation, V.P.I., E.B. Norris, Director (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Resolutions Committee (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - Retirement (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - Reynolds, Eugene B. (Special Fund), Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Beneficiary (Box 6, Folder 74)
    - R, miscellaneous (Box 6, Folder 75)
    - Salary Schedule (Box 6, Folder 76)
    - Scholarships, Fellowships, and Loans (Box 6, Folder 77)
    - Slusher, Clarice, Registrar (Box 6, Folder 78)
    - Southern Conference (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Southern Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Special Committee, Military and Freshman Division (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - State Department of Education, General Correspondence (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - State Department of Education, Granville P. Meade Scholarships (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - State Department of Education, Virginia Advisory Committee on Schools and Colleges (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Statistics Department (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Student Activities Committee, L.A. Pardue, Chairman (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Students, General letters to:from (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Student Life Committee (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Student Organizations (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Summer Conferences (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Swink, H.W., Purchasing and Personnel (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - T, miscellaneous (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - U.S. Department of Agriculture (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - U, miscellaneous (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Vandenburg, H.P.C., Institutional Engineer (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Virginia Advisory Legislative Council (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Virginia Agricultural Conference Board (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Virginia State Board of Agriculture (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Virginia Truck Experiment Station (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - V, miscellaneous (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Whittemore, J.W. (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - W, miscellaneous (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - YMCA, Paul Derring, Secretary (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Young, H.N., Acting Dean of Agriculture (Box 7, Folder 28)
    - Young, H.N., Director, Agricultural Extension Service (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - General Correspondence, 1953
    - Accrediting, National Commission on (Box 7, Folder 30)
    - Agricultural/Vocational Education Department, Curriculum Development (Box 7, Folder 31)
    - Athletic Association, Virginia Tech (Box 7, Folder 32)
    - Attorney General J.L. Almond (Box 7, Folder 33)
    - Audit (Box 7, Folder 34)
    - Band, V.P.I. (Box 7, Folder 35)
    - Budget Matters (Box 7, Folder 36)
    - Cassell, S.K., Business Manager (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - Cato, W.H., Director, Guidance and Placement (Box 7, Folder 38)
    - Chemical Engineering Department, Curriculum Development (Box 7, Folder 39)
    - Commandant of Cadets, Major General J.M. Devine (Box 7, Folder 40)
    - Commencement Exercises (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Community Concert Association (Box 7, Folder 42)
    - Dairy Department, G.C. Graf, Head (Box 7, Folder 43)
    - Daughtrey, W.H., Director, Extension (Box 7, Folder 44)
    - Dietrick, L.B. (Box 7, Folder 45)
    - Dietrick, L.B., Dean of Agriculture (Box 7, Folder 46)
    - E, miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Educational Foundation, V.P.I. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Educational Foundation, V.P.I., Scholarships (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Electrical Engineering Department (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Engineering Experiment Station (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - English and Foreign Language Department (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Enrollment Statistics (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Extension Division, General Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Extension, Danville (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Extension, Norfolk (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Extension, Richmond (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - F, miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - Faculty Committees (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Faculty Lists (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Farrier, P.H., Director, Admissions (Box 8, Folder 15)
    - Football (Box 8, Folder 16)
    - General Assembly Members Visiting Campus (Box 8, Folder 17)
    - General Education Board (Box 8, Folder 18)
    - Geology Department (Box 8, Folder 19)
    - Gifts to the College (Box 8, Folder 20)
    - Governor of Virginia, John S. Battle (Box 8, Folder 21)
    - Graduate Committee (see also Pardue, L.A.) (Box 8, Folder 22)
    - Graphics Department (Box 8, Folder 23)
    - Guthridge, J.W., Director of Civilian Students (Box 8, Folder 24)
    - Hutcheson, J.R., Chancellor (Box 8, Folder 25)
    - H, miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 26)
    - Hardy, J.E., Director of Dormitories (Box 8, Folder 27)
    - Hart, Harris, Director of Personnel (Box 8, Folder 28)
    - Harrison, E.D., Assistant Dean of Engineering (Box 8, Folder 29)
    - High School Day Committee (Box 8, Folder 30)
    - Home Economics Department (Box 8, Folder 31)
    - Honor Court (Box 8, Folder 32)
    - Horticulture Department (Box 8, Folder 33)
    - Industrial Engineering Department (Box 8, Folder 34)
    - Infirmary, Dr. C.R. Lyons, Physician (Box 8, Folder 35)
    - J, miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 36)
    - Jewish Holidays (Box 8, Folder 37)
    - Johnston, G. Burke (Box 8, Folder 38)
    - K, miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 39)
    - Legislation (Box 8, Folder 40)
    - L, miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 41)
    - Motion Picture Unit, Progress Report (Box 8, Folder 42)
    - N, miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 43)
    - National Collegiate Athletic Association (Box 8, Folder 44)
    - Pardue, L.A., Director of Graduate Studies (Box 8, Folder 45)
    - Pardue, L.A., Vice-President (Box 8, Folder 46)
    - Pasture Improvement Committee (Box 8, Folder 47)
    - Physics Department, F.L. Robeson, Head (Box 8, Folder 48)
    - President's Council (Box 8, Folder 49)
    - Price, H.L. (Box 8, Folder 50)
    - R, miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - Radford College, Coordination with V.P.I. (Box 8, Folder 52)
    - Radford College, Woman's Division of V.P.I. (Box 8, Folder 53)
    - Radford College, Dr. Charles K. Martin, President (Box 8, Folder 54)
    - Regional Council for Education (Box 8, Folder 55)
    - Research Foundation, Virginia Polytechnic Institute, E.B. Norris, Director (Box 8, Folder 56)
    - Resolutions Committee (Box 8, Folder 57)
    - S, miscellaneous (Williams Hall Dedication Speech) (Box 8, Folder 58)
    - Scholarships, Fellowships, and Loans (Box 8, Folder 59)
    - Southern Athletic Conference (Box 8, Folder 60-61)
    - Southern Conference Presidents (Box 8, Folder 62)
    - Southern Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools (Box 8, Folder 63)
    - Special Committee, Military and Freshman Division Program (Box 8, Folder 64)
    - State Department of Education, Advisory Committee on Schools and Colleges (Box 8, Folder 65)
    - State Department of Education, General Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 66)
    - Statistics Department, Boyd Harshbarger, Head (Box 8, Folder 67)
    - Student Activities Committee, L.A. Pardue, Chairman (Box 8, Folder 68)
    - Swink, H.W., Purchasing and Personnel (Box 8, Folder 69)
    - T, miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 70)
    - Tennessee Valley Authority (Box 8, Folder 71)
    - Treasurer of Virginia (Box 8, Folder 72)
    - V, miscellaneous (Box 8, Folder 73)
    - Virginia Advisory Legislative Council (Box 8, Folder 74)
    - Virginia Agricultural Conference Board (Box 8, Folder 75)
    - Virginia Truck Experiment Station, Audit (Box 8, Folder 76)
    - Virginia State Board of Agriculture (Box 8, Folder 77)
    - YMCA, Paul Derring Secretary (Box 8, Folder 78)
    - Young, H.N., Director, Agricultural Experiment Station, Biennial Budget (Box 8, Folder 79)
  - General Correspondence, 1954
    - A, miscellaneous (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Accrediting, National Commission on (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Advisory Committee (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Agricultural Economics and Rural Sociology Department, H.M. Love, Head (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Agricultural Engineering Department (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Agricultural :Vocational Education Department, H.W. Sanders, Head (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Agronomy Department (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Alumni Association, General; H.B. Redd, Secretary (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Alumni Association, Fund Council (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Alumni Association, World War II Memorial (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Athletic Association, Virginia Tech (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Attorney General J. Lindsay Almond (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Biology Department, I. D. Wilson, Head (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Bradford, J.H., Director of State Budget (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Budget Allotment (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Budget Matters (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Business Administration Department, T.W. Knote, Head (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Cadet Corps (Box 9, Folder 18)
    - Capital Outlay Needs (Box 9, Folder 19)
    - Cassell, S.K., Business Manager (Box 9, Folder 20)
    - Cato, W.H., Director of Guidance and Placement (Box 9, Folder 21)
    - Chemical Engineering Department, F.C. Vilbrandt, Head (Box 9, Folder 22)
    - Chemistry Department, J.W. Watson, Head (Box 9, Folder 23)
    - Civil Engineering Department, C.W. Brinker, Head (Box 9, Folder 24)
    - College Calendar (Box 9, Folder 25)
    - Commandant of Cadets, Major General J.M. Devine (Box 9, Folder 26)
    - Commencement Exercises (Box 9, Folder 27)
    - Cregger, S. G., Auditor (Box 9, Folder 28)
    - Davis, Miss Georgie T. (Box 9, Folder 29)
    - Dietrick, L.B., Dean of Agriculture (Box 9, Folder 30)
    - Educational Foundation, Virginia Polytechnic Institute (Box 9, Folder 31-32)
    - Educational Foundation, Virginia Polytechnic Institute, Scholarships (Box 9, Folder 33)